[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What important vitamin does asparagus contain?", "correct_answer": "Vitamin B9", "incorrect_answers": ["Vitamin PP", "Vitamin K", "Vitamin D"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This medical term is defined as the abnormal fear of darkness, and commonly experienced by children.", "correct_answer": "Nyctophobia", "incorrect_answers": ["Cynophobia", "Nightophobia", "Zoophobia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these lizard species is not endangered?", "correct_answer": "Eastern Bearded Dragon", "incorrect_answers": ["Blunt-nosed Leopard Lizard", "Mona Ground Iguana", "Komodo Dragon"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Corruption scandals and false allegations affect a New York City policeman and his family in Pride and Glory. It stars Edward Norton, Colin Farrell and this great actor from Seinfeld.\u201d", "correct_answer": "Jon Voight", "incorrect_answers": ["Reni Santoni", "Gene Hackman", "Wayne Knight"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "You go into a diner and  you hear the  waitress yell out Cats Eyes. What has someone just ordered?", "correct_answer": "tapioca", "incorrect_answers": ["a breakfast of steak and two eggs", "strawberries and cream", "sunny side eggs"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Paprika, and chili peppers in general, are very high in this essential vitamin.", "correct_answer": "Vitamin C", "incorrect_answers": ["Vitamin A", "Vitamin E", "Vitamin B5"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The first screen kiss was seen in the short movie The Kiss, shown in what year?", "correct_answer": "1896", "incorrect_answers": ["1919", "1882", "1912"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "During what historical period is the 1962 movie To Kill a Mockingbird set?", "correct_answer": "The Great Depression", "incorrect_answers": ["The Vietnam War", "The Jazz Age", "The Second World War"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Sugar is a major reason for tooth decay.   Due to the high content of sugar in most carbonated drinks, you can diminish the risk of tooth decay by sipping through a straw.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What Alfred Hitchcock movie starred Ingrid Bergman as the daughter of a convicted Nazi spy, and Cary Grant as government agent T.R. Devlin?", "correct_answer": "Notorious", "incorrect_answers": ["The Man Who Knew Too Much", "Shadow of a Doubt", "Vertigo"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Where was the worlds first modern electrically air-conditioned building located?", "correct_answer": "San Antonio, Texas", "incorrect_answers": ["Rome, Italy", "New York, New York", "Barcelona, Spain"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This actor, who portrayed Mr. McCardle, Juror #9 in 12 Angry Men, passed away in 1964 after a brilliant career in early television and motion pictures.", "correct_answer": "Joseph Sweeney", "incorrect_answers": ["John Fiedler", "Ed Begley", "Jack Warden"]}]